[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1938 Doug Corrigan set out on a flight from New York to California. What nickname did he get after the flight?", "correct_answer": "Wrong Way Corrigan", "incorrect_answers": ["Day/Night  Corrigan", "California DreaminCorrigan", "All-the-Way Corrigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of the following movies did Scarlett Johansson appear?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Black Dahlia", "The Island", "The Prestige"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are pangolins related to anteaters and armadillos?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the place of rabbits in Japanese tradition and mythology?", "correct_answer": "They are believed to inhabit the Moon.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are despised as being too timid.", "They are considered omnipotent.", "Rabbits are not a part of Japanese mythology."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the second US President  to face impeachment?", "correct_answer": "William Clinton", "incorrect_answers": ["William Blount", "Andrew Johnson", "Richard Nixon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of insect is the Orange Tip?", "correct_answer": "Butterfly", "incorrect_answers": ["Grasshopper", "Ladybug", "Moth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What planet does Obi Wan tell Luke to go to while he is lying in the snow?", "correct_answer": "Dagobagh", "incorrect_answers": ["Tattooine", "Naboo", "Coruscant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Both male and female reindeer grow antlers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Bourne Ultimatum, the character played by David Straihtirn, is trying to start his own operation. What is ti called?", "correct_answer": "Blackbriar", "incorrect_answers": ["Martyn III", "Threadway II", "Tritent II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following persons was not a Prime Minister of Israel?", "correct_answer": "Chaim Weizmann", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Netanyahu", "Moshe Sharett", "Ehud Barak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was  the first Major League Baseball player to hit four homers in one game and three triples in another game?", "correct_answer": "Willie Mays", "incorrect_answers": ["Mickey Mantle", "Tris Speaker", "Joe Dimaggio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from J. R. R. Tolkien\u2019s The Lord of The Rings: The Two Towers was also known as Fangorn and was the oldest of his kind?", "correct_answer": "Treebeard", "incorrect_answers": ["Th\u00e9oden", "Tobold Old Toby Hornblower", "Tom Bombadil"]}]